[
  { 
    "id": 1, 
    "front": "cat", 
    "back": "кот",
    "setName": "English"
  },
  { 
    "id": 2, 
    "front": "book", 
    "back": "книга",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 3, 
    "front": "tree", 
    "back": "дерево",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 4, 
    "front": "car", 
    "back": "машина",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 5, 
    "front": "sky", 
    "back": "небо",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 6, 
    "front": "coffee", 
    "back": "кофе",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 7, 
    "front": "window", 
    "back": "окно",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 8, 
    "front": "friend", 
    "back": "друг",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 9, 
    "front": "music", 
    "back": "музыка",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 10, 
    "front": "phone", 
    "back": "телефон",
    "setName": "English" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 11, 
    "front": "border", 
    "back": "граница",
    "setName": "css-свойства" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 12, 
    "front": "display", 
    "back": "отображение",
    "setName": "css-свойства" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 13, 
    "front": "color", 
    "back": "цвет текста",
    "setName": "css-свойства" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 14, 
    "front": "font-size", 
    "back": "размер шрифта",
    "setName": "css-свойства" 
  },
  { 
    "id": 15, 
    "front": "width", 
    "back": "ширина",
    "setName": "css-свойства" 
  }
]